brighthubpm.com 2012-10-06

# Bright Hub Project Management - Privacy Policy

**Effective as of: January 1, 2012**

This is the privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) for Bright Hub, Inc. (“Bright Hub”, "we", "us" or "our") websites (collectively, "Site"). We provide this Privacy Policy to inform you of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personal information we receive from users of www.brighthubpm.com. Our Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time, and we will notify you of any material changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on the Site.

## INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE

### Personally Identifiable Information

During your interactions with the Site, such as when you register with the Site, Bright Hub may collect personally identifiable information, such as your name, date of birth, postal address, email address, and telephone number. We use this information to validate Site users and facilitate participation in various Bright Hub services as specified on the Site. If we need to contact you regarding the Site, our services, your account or your use of the Site, this information may be used to contact you. If you send us e-mail, we will retain your email and any applicable response in order to handle any follow-up questions you may have and to measure how effectively we address your concerns. Bright Hub retains such personally identifiable information only for as long as is necessary depending on the reason for your submission, and collects no more personally identifiable information than is reasonably necessary to provide you with the services for which such information is collected.

### Non-Personally Identifiable Information

To help us enhance and optimize users' overall Site experience, we may collect non-personally identifiable information during your visit. Examples of non-personally-identifiable information may include your Internet access provider, your computer’s Internet protocol (IP) address, your user profile, your browser and operating system, the date and time of your visit, and data based on your use of the Site. Bright Hub collects non-personally-identifiable information in order to, among other things, provide you with or assist in the provision of information through the Site and to maintain the performance of the Site. This data is not associated with any of your personal information and is not shared with any third parties.

### Disclosure of Information to Third Party Vendors

Bright Hub may also use third party advertisers and service providers to help present customized content and advertisements on the Site. These providers may use cookies, web beacons, or other similar tools on your computer to help present, better target, and measure the effectiveness of their content and advertisements, using data gathered over time and across their networks of Web pages to determine or predict the characteristics and preferences of their audience. Bright Hub may share certain non-personally identifiable information about you as a Site user with certain advertisers and service providers to help them deliver more relevant content and advertisements through their networks. These nonaffiliated third parties may include, but are not limited to: (i) vendors; (ii) retailers; and (iii) online advertising agencies and direct marketers, including without limitation telemarketers. These parties may compensate us for your information. We may also disclose the information to investors, potential investors, business partners and others. The use of cookies, web beacons, or other similar tools by these advertisers and providers is subject to their own privacy policies, not Bright Hub’s.

### Consumer Opt-out Choices

Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. Although no personally identifying information is collected by our cookies, if you prefer, you can set your browser to reject cookies, or to reject third party cookies only. If you reject cookies, you may not be able to sign in or use other features of websites that rely on cookies to enable the user experience. If you do not wish to have information about your activities traveling to and from our Site to be collected by our third party partners, you can opt-out of different ad networks below:

Network Advertising Alliance — an association of advertising networks, data exchanges, and marketing analytics services providers provides information to consumers about internet advertising practices. Click [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/index.asp) to learn more about the practice of collecting and using non-personally identifiable information and the choices you have about these tools.

Advertising Option Program — an online behavioral advertising industry self regulatory program. Click [here](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/)

Yahoo Analytics — Click [here](http://info.yahoo.com/privacy/us/yahoo/opt_out/targeting/details.html)

Google Advertising FAQs and Opt-out — Click [here](http://www.google.com/intl/en/privacy/ads/)

DoubleClick Interest-Based Advertising — Click [here](http://www.google.com/intl/en/privacy/ads/)

## SECURITY

### Encryption

Bright Hub takes extensive precautions to protect our users' information, both online and offline.

If you submit sensitive personal information through the Site such as credit card information, we have implemented what we believe to be industry-standard robust encryption in order to help us keep your information secure and accurate.

### Additional Safeguards

Bright Hub maintains physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect the confidentiality and security of any personally identifiable information that you disclose to Bright Hub. Bright Hub utilizes what Bright Hub believes to be industry best security measures to protect personally identifiable information under Bright Hub’s control, and Bright Hub limits access to your personally identifiable information within Bright Hub and Bright Hub’s affiliates to those employees who need to know such personally identifiable information to provide information, services and/or products to you. However, due to the nature of the Internet and computer systems, no transmission of data over the Internet is guaranteed to be completely secure, regardless of Bright Hub’s best intentions. As such, Bright Hub cannot ensure or warrant the security of any personally identifiable information you transmit to Bright Hub.

### External Links or References

The Site may contain links or references to other parties' sites, including sponsors of Bright Hub or Bright Hub’s services. Bright Hub is not responsible for the privacy or other practices of any such outside sites, and Bright Hub expressly disclaims any and all liability related to such sites. We encourage our users to consider this before deciding to visit such outside sites and to read the applicable privacy policies and terms of use of each such site.

## COMMUNICATIONS FROM BRIGHT HUB

We send all new members a welcome email. From time to time, we will also send email notification, mail or call you to provide you with information concerning updates or enhancements to our service, account issues, or service-related announcements. Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to deactivate your account.

## DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION

### Disclosure to Agents of BRIGHT HUB

From time to time, Bright Hub may share the information you provide to Bright Hub, including personally identifiable information, with outside contractors, auditors, consultants, or others hired by Bright Hub to assist in providing financial or operational activities on Bright Hub’s behalf. Bright Hub requires these parties to use such personally identifiable information only for an authorized purpose on behalf of Bright Hub and consistent with this Privacy Policy.

### Opting In Through Other Venues

Please be advised that if you provide consent and allow Bright Hub to disclose your personally identifiable information through one Bright Hub venue (such as the Site), you will be deemed to have “opted in” through all Bright Hub venues.

### Legal Proceedings

Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law or where we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on us.

### Business Transitions

In the event Bright Hub goes through a business transition, such as a merger, being acquired by another company, bankruptcy, or selling a portion of its assets, users' personally identifiable information may be part of the assets transferred.

## VERIFYING AND UPDATING INFORMATION

### Verification

We use outside sources to verify a user's accounting credentials to validate that users access to our system.

### Correcting/Updating/Deleting/Deactivating Personal Information

A user may review, request corrections, ask that we delete, or refuse further collection or use of the personally identifiable information Bright Hub collects from such user. Such user may do this by contacting Bright Hub using the contact information provided at the end of this document.

## GENERAL

### Privacy Policy Changes

Our Privacy Policy is intended to provide you with a safe and secure experience. We reserve the right to change, modify, add or remove portions of our Privacy Policy at any time without prior notice at our sole discretion. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes to this Privacy Policy, on the Site and other places we deem appropriate. We will use information in accordance with the Privacy Policy under which the information was collected. All Privacy Policy changes are effective immediately upon posting. The last date on which this Privacy Policy has been updated is noted above.

### Consent to Receive Notices Via the Site

Users who register with the Site are agreeing that Bright Hub may deliver all privacy and opt out notices to you in the manners described in this Section (GENERAL).

### Web Logs and Other Forums

The Site may offer web logs, web postings, bulletin boards, chat rooms, newsgroups or other forums which permit users to interact online. Any information you transmit online in such forums will be made public and Bright Hub cannot control nor is it responsible for the use any third party may make of such information

## CONTACT INFORMATION

Questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy should be directed to Bright Hub using the following contact information:

Postal Address:

Privacy Matters c/o Bright Hub, Inc.   
270 River Street, Suite 405   
Troy, NY 12180   
Email: [privacy@brighthub.com](mailto:privacy@brighthub.com)   
Telephone: +1 (518) 833-0233   
Fax: +1 (703) 738-1772 

## LIMITATION OF LIABILITY

YOU UNDERSTAND AND AGREE THAT ANY DISPUTE OVER PRIVACY IS SUBJECT TO THE TERMS AND CONDITION OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND BRIGHT HUB Project Management’S [TERMS OF USE](http://www.brighthubpm.com/content/terms/) (INCLUDING ANY INDEMNIFICATION AND LIMITATIONS ON DAMAGES CONTAINED THEREIN).
